Finding Aid for the The Vanderbilt University Reunions
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
The Andrew Nelson Lytle 1988 Addition
undate
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0474
.42 linear feet
- Classes of 1891, 1896 (Folder 1)
- Classes of 1898, 1904, 1914, 1916 (Folder 2)
- Classes of 1917, 1919 (Folder 3)
  See also article in Tennessean June 7, 1942 -"Grads of '17 To Be Guests"
- Classes of, 1921-1923 (Folder 4)
- Classes of 1924-1925 (Folder 5)
  See also articles in Banner
  June 9, 1924 -"Commencement Is Inaugurated" Tennessean June 11, 1924 - “Interesting Social Courtesies EXtended James W. Gerard,“ “Gerard Visits Jackson's Home,“ and “James W. Gerard Has Very Busy Day Here“
- Classes of 1930, 1931, 1932, 1930 and 1938 Reunion (Folder 6)
  May 5, 1938 - "Finals Speakers at Vanderbilt"
  May 6, 1938 - "Army Medical Course Planned at Vanderbilt"
  June 1, 1938 - "Vanderbilt Commencement Program Fullest in History of University"
  June 4, 1938 - "Vanderbilt Students, Alumni Ready for Graduation Week"
  June 7, 1938 - "Commencement Clinic Held at Vanderbilt," "New Vanderbilt Hospital Unit Ready for Inspection," "Vanderbilt Alumni Elect 5 to Board"
  June 8, 1938 - "Seniors View Days of Past" "Student Council at Vanderbilt Gives Tea"
  Tennessean
  June 5, 1938 - "Alumni Commencement Clinic Opens at Vanderbilt on Monday" "Six Winners of Vanderbilt Founder's Medals Announced"
  June 7,1938 -Class of '78 picture; article on page 9 "Carmichael Cites Joint University Library Need"
  June 8,1938-"Seniors View Days of Past" "Student Council at Vanderbilt Gives Tea"
  Tennessean, June 5, 1938 -"Alumni Commencement Clinic Opens at Vanderbilt on Monday" "Six Winners of Vanderbilt Founder's Medals Announced"
  June 8,1938 -"348 to Receive Degrees Today at Vanderbilt"
- Class of 1946 and 1946 Reunion; Class of 1947 and 1947 Reunion, Class of 1951 (Folder 7)
  March 25, 1946 - "Commencement Procession Held Despite Rain"
  April 24,1946 - "Vanderbilt Honor Candidates Announced"
  May 3, 1946 - "Vanderbilt Commencement Speakers For Ceremonies June 9, 10 Announced"
  May 24, 1946 - "Vanderbilt Graduation Events Set" June 3, 1946 - "Class Reunions to Feature Alumni Day at Vanderbilt"
  June 5, 1946 - "Vanderbilt to Honor War Dead in Week-End Service"
  June 8, 1946 - "Alumni Hold Reunions at Vanderbilt
  June 10, 1946 - "Vanderbilt Alumni Hear Role Cited, Name New Officials" "Vanderbilt Awards Degrees, Lists Honors"
  June 13, 1946 - "Vanderbilt Medical Alumni Hold 40th Reunion"
  June 2, 1946 - "VU Reunions Set Saturday"
  June 9, 1946 - "Charles Ragland to Head Vanderbilt Alumni Body" "Eating, Chatting, Nostalgia Mark Vanderbilt Reunions" "Vanderbilt Presents Diplomas to Graduates"
  June 11, 1946 - "Vanderbilt Grads Hear Dr. Hill"
  Banner
  April 3, 1947 - "Vanderbilt Alumni Discuss Class Reunion Plans"
  April 6, 1947 - VU Speaker
  Vanderbilt Alumnus
  June 1947
- Reunions:, 1950, 1952-1954 (Folder 8)
  March 10, 1950 - "Texan to Deliver Commencement Sermon at V. U."
  Feb. 20, 1950 - "Committee Heads Named for VU Alumni Reunion"
  Feb. 25, 1950 - "Discuss Next Class Get-Together" "Vanderbilt Alumni Plan Spring Reunion
- Reunions:, 1955-1957 (Folder 9)
  See also article in Banner
  June 3, 1957 - page 8
- Reunions:, 1958-1959, 1969 (Folder 10)
  See also articles in Tennessean
  May 31, 1958 - "Old Grads Meet"
  "Old Grads, Seniors Make VU Hum"
  "Friends Meet at Medical School"
- Quinq Club Reunions (Folder 11)
  June 3, 1948 - "Quinq Club to Receive New Members"
  June 5, 1948 - "Quinq Club Holds Meeting at Vanderbilt"
  June 7, 1969 - "SO-Year Alumni of Vanderbilt Inducted Into Club"
  June 1947, July-August 1948, June 1949
- Basketball Reunions:, 1958, 1962 (Folder 12)
  Jan. 27, 1958 - page 16
  Feb. 8, 1958 - page 7
  Feb. 10, 1958 - page 20
  Feb. 15, 1958 - page 7
  Feb. 17, 1958 - page 16
  Tennessean, Feb. 8, 1958 - page 10
  Feb. 9, 1958 - page 3-E
  Feb. 23, 1958 - "Among Us Fans"
- 50th Reunion of 1915 Football Team
  See article in the Banner Sept. 18, 1965 Vanderbilt's Football Champions of 1915 in 50th Reunion Celebration"
  Class of 1899 See article in the Tennessean June 10, 1924 - "Law Class of '99 in Banquet Recalls 'Incident of the Poker